{
    "id": "2087954e0e674958801a8313330b5d16",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We had a good ……………………………. of football.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "game",
                "match"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5ae107d6dea4e3cabf41afd2f67ebb4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wants a …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pair of new shoes",
                "new pair of shoes"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3510c7da102d4168aef451ca07a25c33"
        },
        {
            "question": "He enquired about …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your state of health",
                "the state of your health"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c70b7004508c48c6bd102767fc2a0578"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………… of Chennai does not suit me.",
            "description": "Climate is what the weather is like over a long period of time. ",
            "answers": [
                "weather",
                "climate"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f29e5348f32146c6982d7554f9716643"
        },
        {
            "question": "He gave me some sound …………………………….",
            "description": "Advice is a noun advise is the verb advice does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "advice",
                "advices",
                "advise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d461b8f94343478cae1a53dfbc2f38d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news …………………………. true.",
            "description": "News is singular in English.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c27ced242fd24eb783bd45db7524d4be"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has two …………………………… hens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dozens",
                "dozen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1f1a3e5cc21414fb46a230d1d558a51"
        },
        {
            "question": "The …………………………. grazing",
            "description": "Cattle is plural it is used with a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "cattle is",
                "cattles are",
                "cattle are"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ec8e6e74a05c46fdbc4e7a0628934263"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my brothers ………………………… a doctor.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after one of.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e45aae539451451f96bcf26169ac9ddd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some of my friends ………………………….. to join the army.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb after some of. ",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b16b933c98042a58311309316d64e34"
        },
        {
            "question": "He took offence …………………………. my innocent remarks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ab61eb133f1404f83dc1bb73d6069a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich man didn’t give the beggar …………………………..",
            "description": "Use anything in negative sentences. Not anything means the same as nothing. ",
            "answers": [
                "something",
                "anything",
                "nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e96003949c545e7ba155bf5164b7d0f"
        }
    ]
}